Marist Student Government Association Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 20. 2004
  - Subseries 20.5: Reports
    - Committee A - Core Curriculum (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Committee B Guiding Principles (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Core Committee A (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Core Models Committee A (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Core Models Committee A Attachments (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - DUCSA Constitution (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Stop Hazing (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - 2004 Strategic Planning (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Subseries 20.6: Correspondence
    - Pay for Print Correspondence, March 19, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Core Curriculum Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Subseries 20.7: Misc.
    - Pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Bobbi Sue Gibbons for Student Body President (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - School of Social and Behavioral Sciences (Box 15, Folder 69)
- 21. 2005
  - Subseries 21.1: Meetings
    - Academic Council Meetings (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Club Affairs Council Meeting, October 12, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - School of Social and Behavioral Sciences Meetings (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 21.2: Legislation
    - Alternative Energy Resolution, May 3, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Elections Reform Act of 2005, August 31, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, September 7, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Creation of the Student Speaks Committee, September 14, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Creation of the Recycling Committee Bill, September 19, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - The Expansion Contract of 2005, September 28, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Legislation, November 16, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Legislation, November 30, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Legislation, December 7, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Re-Allocation for Fall 2005 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 21.3: Clubs
    - Circle K - President's Council, September 16-18, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 21.4: Allocations
    Extent: 69 folders
    - Accounting Club Allocations (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Advertising Club Allocations (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Alpha Kappa Psi Allocations (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - American Chemical Society Allocations (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - ARCO Allocations (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Band Allocations (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Bowling Club Allocations (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - BSU Allocations (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Business Club Allocations (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Chess Club Allocations (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Circle K Allocations (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Class of 2005 Allocations (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Class of 2006 Allocations (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Class of 2007 Allocations (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Class of 2008 Allocations (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Communication Arts Society Allocations (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Criminal Justice Society Allocations (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Dance Club Allocations (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Economics Club Allocations, Fall 2005 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Equestrian Club Allocations, Spring 2005 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Fencing Allocations (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Fox P.A.W. Allocations (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Gaelic Society Allocations (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Gender Equality Club Allocations (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Greek Council Allocations (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Habitat for Humanity Allocations (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - History Club Allocations (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Ice Hockey Allocations (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Illegible Allocations (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - IT Allocations (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - International Club Allocations (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Italian American Soc. Allocations (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Kappa Kappa Psi/Tau Beta Sigma Joint Allocations (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Kappa Lambda Psi Allocations (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Lambda Pi Eta Allocations (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Literary Arts Society Allocations (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - McCann Clubs Allocations (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Phi Kappa Sigma Allocations (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Pi Sigma Alpha (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Political Science Club Allocations (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Psychology Club Allocations, Fall 2005 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Women's Rugby Allocations (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - SGA Allocations (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - SHRM Allocations (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Student Life Council Allocations (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Tau Beta Sigma Allocations (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Marist Singers Allocations (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Ski Team Allocations (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Volleyball Club Allocations (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Zeta Psi Allocations (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 21.5: Reports
    - Financial Board Guidelines and Procedures, September 1, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Report on the Five Year Master Plan, October 31, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Committee B Core Curriculum Proposals and Drafts (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Individual Goals for the Juaras Administration (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Conflict of Interest Policy (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 21.6: Correspondence
    - Resignation Letter, April 2, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 21.7: Misc.
    - Elliot Spitzer Informational Pamphlets, June 1, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Student Academic Council Executive Board Information (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 22. 2006
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, events, allocations, and correspondence
  - Subseries 22.1: Meetings
    - Ethics Campaign Meeting with Steve Sansola, April 20, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 22.2: Legislation
    - Bill to Charter the Marist College Rugby Football Club, February 6, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Re-Allocation for Spring 2006, March 1, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Legislation, May 5, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Creation of the General Member Committee, August 30, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Legislation, October 4, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Branch Communication Facilitation Act, November 8, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Impeachment and Removal From Office Overhaul Amendment, November 29, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 22.3: Clubs
    - Alumni Association By-laws, March 1, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 22.4: Events
    - 2006 Spring Elections, Spring 2006 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 22.5: Allocations
    - SGA Expenses 2006 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 22.6: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Resignation Letters (Box 18, Folder 30)
- 23. 2007
  - Subseries 23.1: Meetings
    - Alumni Executive Board Meeting, October 6, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Board of Trustees Executive Meeting, April 5, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 5, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, June 7, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, September 15, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, November 10, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meetings 1 of 2, January 24 - March 7, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Executive Board Meetings 2 of 2, March 7 - December 5, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Summer Meetings (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 23.2: Legislation
    - Legislation, February 7, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Committee for American Troop Support, February 14, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Legislation, March 21, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Legislation, May 2, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Marist College School Spirit Committee Legislation, Spring 2007 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Circle K Guides (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Circle K - Harvest Festival Flyer, October 31, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Animal Shelter Volunteering Event Evaluation, Fall 2007 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - SGA Transition Dinner (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - SGA Tentative Fall Schedule (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Transportation Policies for Organizations (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 23.3: Clubs
    - Circle K Guides (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Circle K - Harvest Festival Flyer, October 31, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Transportation Policies for Organizations (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 23.4: Events
    - Animal Shelter Volunteering Event Evaluation, Fall 2007 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - SGA Transition Dinner (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 23.5: Reports
    - SGA Tentative Fall Schedule (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Subseries 23.6: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Subseries 23.7: Misc.
    - Position Applications (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Sodexho Invoice - Omar Diaz (Box 19, Folder 32)
- 24. 2008
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, clubs, events, allocations, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 24.1: Meetings
    - Board of Trustees Meetings (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Subseries 24.2: Clubs
    - Board of Trustees By-laws (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Subseries 24.3: Events
    - NRHH Induction Ceremony (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Subseries 24.4: Allocations
    Extent: 18 folders
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Class of 2013 Allocations (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Pi Alpha Theta Allocations (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Phi Sigma Alpha Allocations (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Political Science Club Allocations (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Psychology Club Allocations (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Public Relations Society Allocations (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - SHRM Allocations (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Sigma Tau Delta Allocations (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Student Booster Club Allocations (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Subseries 24.5: Reports
    - Dennis Murray: Spring Update on College Activities, January 22, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Freshman Deposit Trend Analysis, May 1, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Planning, Assessment, and Continuous Improvement at Marist College (pages 13-17), May 13, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Dennis Murray: Fall Update on College Activities, September 8, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 24.6: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 24.7: Misc.
    - Candidates for Executive Board Appointments (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Copy Job Request Form, November 30, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - President Erik Zeyher Speeches (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Student Body President Omar Diaz Speeches (Box 20, Folder 9)
- 25. 2009
  - Subseries 25.1: Meetings
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - SLC Meetings (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 25.2: Legislation
    - Legislation, April 8, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Creation of Constitution and Bylaws Revision Committee, April 15, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Legislation, February 24, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Bill for Town-Hall Committee, October 7, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Bill to Recognize Phi Kappa Sigma Fraternity as Colony Status, November 4, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Resolution to Extend Library Hours, November 11, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 25.3: Clubs
    - Circle K - Misc. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Student Programming Council By-laws, December 2, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 25.4: Events
    - Patty Hendrikson Speaking Engagement, July 16, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - The Fresh Air Fund, July 24, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Dutchess County Fair Group Rates, August 1, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - 5th Annual SLC Leadership Conference, October 9, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - ASGA's National Student Summit, Fall 2009 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - SPC Training Agenda (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 25.5: Allocations
    Extent: 84 folders
    - Advertising Club Allocations (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Alpha Kappa Psi Allocations (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Alpha Phi Sigma Allocations (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - American Society Allocations (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - ARCO Allocations (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Athletic Training Club, April 28, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Band Allocations (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Blank Budget Allocation Forms, Fall 2009 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Bowling Club Allocations (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - BSU Allocations (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Business Club Allocations (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Check Request for Clubs/SGA Transparency + Example Form (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Marist College Check Request Transparency (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Marist Cheer Allocations (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Circle K Allocations (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Class of '09 Allocations (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Class of '10 Allocations (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Class of '11 Allocations, May 4, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Class of 2012 Allocations (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Class of '13 Allocations (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Communication Arts Society Allocations, April 8, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Criminal Justice Society Allocations (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Dance Club Allocations (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Equestrian Team Allocations (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Fencing Club Allocations (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Financial Board Workshop Powerpoint, September 9, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Financial Board Workshop Attendance List, September 10, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Fox P.A.W. Allocations (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Gaelic Society Allocations (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Generator Magazine Allocations, November 16, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Greek Advisory Council Allocations (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Greek Music Society Allocations (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Habitat for Humanity Allocations (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - History Club Allocations (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - How To Fill Out: A Budget Allocation (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Italian American Society Allocations (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - International Students Club Allocations (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Kappa Lambda Psi Allocations (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Literary Arts Society Allocations (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Marist College Operating Budget (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Petty Cash Request Transparency and Example Form (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Phi Alpha Theta Allocations (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Pi Sigma Alpha Allocations, May 1, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - PRSSA Allocations (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Psychology Club Allocations (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Political Science Club Allocations, November 12, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Purchase Order Request Form Transparency + Example Form (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Marist College Republicans Allocations (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Men's Rugby Allocations (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Women's Rugby Allocations (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - SHRM Allocations, November 9, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - SIFE Allocations, April 22, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Sigma Tau Delta Allocations (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Ski Team Allocations (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Singers Allocations (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Social Work Club Allocations (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - SAC Allocations, March 30, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Student Booster Club Allocations (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - SGA Allocations (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - SLC Allocations (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Tau Beta Sigma Allocations (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Time Check Allocations, April 22, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Theta Delta Chi Allocations (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Ultimate Frisbee Allocations (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Unknown Allocations (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Subseries 25.6: Reports
    - Student Survey Answers, Spring 2009 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - What Student Government Can Do Better, Spring 2009 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Official Guidelines for Websites, September 9, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Club Affairs Extended Board Report, September 23, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - CFO Manual - Alyssa Bradt (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Financial Board Guidelines (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Subseries 25.7: Correspondence
    - Club Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence - Steve Townsend (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Delta Iota Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Subseries 25.8: Misc.
    Extent: 12 folders
    - Chief Justice Morgan Nederhood Resignation Address, January 21, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Steve Townsend Inauguration Speech, April 3, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Financial Board Notes, October 5, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Steve Townsend Marist Minute Article, Fall 2009 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Camp Hidden Valley map (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Club Councils List (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - College Activities Activity Codes (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Expense Account Codes (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Marist Health Services Flyer (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Misc. Notes (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Steve Townsend Election Speech (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Tentative Summer Schedule (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Townsend Administration Application for Appointment (Box 21, Folder 66)
- 26. 2010
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, allocations, reports, and misc.
  - Subseries 26.1: Meetings
    - Student Life Committee Meeting, April 14, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 26.2: Legislation
    - Bill to Recognize That Girl Goes Local of the "I Am That Girl" Organization as a Committee, February 3, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Bill to Charter Marist Game Society, February 17, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Bill to Recognize That "To Write Love On Her Arms" Committee as an Organization, February 18, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Addition of Historian Position to the Constitution, April 29, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 26.3: Clubs
    - Game Society By-laws, January 1, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 26.4: Allocations
    Extent: 71 folders
    - Advertising Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Alpha Kappa Psi Allocations (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Alpha Phi Sigma Allocations (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - American Chemical Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Anime Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - ARCO Allocations (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Asian Alliance Allocations (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Athletic Training Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Band Allocations (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - BSU Allocations (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Business Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Chess Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Circle K Allocations (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Class of '10 Allocations (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Class of '11 Allocations (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Class of '12 Allocations (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Class of 2013 Allocations (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Club Affairs Allocations (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Communication Arts Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Criminal Justice Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Dance Ensemble Allocations, Fall 2010 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Fox P.A.W. Allocations (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Game Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Gender Equality Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Generator Magazine Allocations (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Greek Advisory Council Allocations (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Greek Music Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Habitat for Humanity Allocations (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Int'l Italian-American Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - International Students Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Kappa Lambda Psi Allocations (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Lambda Pi Eta Allocations (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - LGSA Allocations (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Literary Arts Society Allocations (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - MCAS Allocations (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Phi Alpha Theta Allocations (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - Pi Sigma Alpha Allocations (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - Political Science Club Allocations (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - PRSSA Allocations (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Psychology Club Allocations (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Red Ink Allocations (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Marist Republicans Allocations (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Men's Rugby Allocations (Box 23, Folder 6)